[{"question": "<p>Given</p><br><pre><code>a = np.linspace(0, 5, 2)<br>b = np.linspace(5, 10, 3)<br>c = np.linspace(10, 15, 5)<br><br>A, _ = np.meshgrid(a, b, c)<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the shape of the array A?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "(3, 2, 5)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "(5, 5, 5)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(2, 3, 5)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(5, 3, 2)", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "<pre><code>A = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])<br>B = np.array([1, 1, 1])<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the shape of 'A+B'?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "(3, 3)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "(1, 3)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(3, 1)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "(1, 1)", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "<pre><code>A = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])<br>B = np.array([1])<br></code></pre><br><p>What is the value of 'A+B'?</p>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "np.array([[2, 2, 3], [5, 5, 6], [8, 8, 9]])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "ValueError: operands could not be broadcast together with shapes (3,3) (1,) ", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 3, 4], [5, 6, 7], [8, 9, 10]])", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([[2, 3, 4], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "Which of the following objective functions will give a correct answer when used with solve_ivp() to solve coupled differential equations?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "<pre><code>def f(t, Sa, Sb):<br>    dSa / dt = eq_1<br>    dSb / dt = eq_2<br>    return(Sa, Sb)<br></code></pre>", "correct": false}, {"answer": "<pre><code>def f(t, S):<br>    Sa = S[0]<br>    Sb = S[1]<br>    dSa / dt = eq_1<br>    dSb / dt = eq_2<br>    return (dSa/dt, dSb/dt)<br></code></pre>", "correct": true}, {"answer": "<pre><code>def f(t, S):<br>    Sa = S[0]<br>    Sb = S[1]<br>    dSa / dt = eq_1<br>    dSb / dt = eq_2<br>    return (S)<br></code></pre>", "correct": false}, {"answer": "<pre><code>def f(t):<br>    dSa / dt = eq_1<br>    dSb / dt = eq_2<br>    return (dSa/dt, dSb/dt)<br></code></pre>", "correct": false}], "tag": "scipy", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "Which of the following are coupled differential equations:<br><br>a: dw/dt = x + y<br>b: dx/dt = 2x + 4w<br>c: dy/dt = x", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "a, b", "correct": false}, {"answer": "b, c", "correct": false}, {"answer": "a, c", "correct": false}, {"answer": "a, b, c", "correct": true}], "tag": "ode", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What will be the value of b: <br><br>a = np.linspace(6, 10, 5)<br>b = *a", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Memory address of 'a'", "correct": false}, {"answer": "6.0  7.0  8.0  9.0  10.0", "correct": false}, {"answer": "SyntaxError", "correct": true}, {"answer": "np.array([6.0, 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, 10.0])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What is the output of:<br><br>a = np.linspace(6, 10, 5)<br>print(*a)", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Memory address of 'a'", "correct": false}, {"answer": "6.0  7.0  8.0  9.0  10.0", "correct": true}, {"answer": "SyntaxError", "correct": false}, {"answer": "np.array([6.0, 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, 10.0])", "correct": false}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "Which of the following are coupled differential equations:<br><br>a: dw/dt = x + w<br>b: dx/dt = 2x + 4w<br>c: dy/dt = 5", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "none are coupled", "correct": false}, {"answer": "a, b, c", "correct": false}, {"answer": "b, c", "correct": false}, {"answer": "a, b", "correct": true}], "tag": "ode", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "Which of the following is true about matplotlib.pyplot.quiver()?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "plt.quiver() requires the values of X and Y both for arrow locations", "correct": false}, {"answer": "cannot be used in 3D", "correct": true}, {"answer": "requires normalized derivative values", "correct": false}, {"answer": "can be used in 2D and 3D both", "correct": false}], "tag": "matplotlib", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}, {"question": "What will be the output of X[:, 2], where<br>X = np.array([[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6], [7, 8, 9]])", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "array([4, 5, 6])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([2, 5, 8])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([1, 2])", "correct": false}, {"answer": "array([3, 6, 9])", "correct": true}], "tag": "arrays", "lecture_file": "04_fode_2"}]